const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "1. What is the capital of France?",
      answer: "Paris",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "2. What is the highest mountain in the world?",
      answer: "Mount Everest",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "3. What is the largest country in the world?",
      answer: "Russia",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "4. What is the currency of Japan?",
      answer: "Japanese yen",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "5. What is the smallest continent in the world?",
      answer: "Australia",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "6. What is the largest ocean in the world?",
      answer: "Pacific Ocean",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "7. What is the official language of Brazil?",
      answer: "Portuguese",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "8. What is the largest desert in the world?",
      answer: "Sahara Desert",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "9. What is the longest river in the world?",
      answer: "Nile River",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "10. What is the smallest country in the world?",
      answer: "Vatican City",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Hard",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "11. What is the capital of Canada?",
      answer: "Ottawa",
      category: "Geography",
      difficulty: "Medium",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/542909/"
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "12. What is the atomic number of Oxygen?",
      answer: "8",
      category: "Chemistry",
      difficulty: "Easy",
      image: "https://source.unsplash.com/collection/325022/"
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: "13. What is the formula for water?",
      answer: "H2O",
      category: "Chemistry",
      difficulty: "Easy"}
  ];
  
  
  export default questions;